

610 Purdue Mall, West Lafayette, IN, 47907

 \square 415-203-8543 | \square chi45@purdue.edu | \blacktriangleleft https://hyung-gun.me | \square stnoah1 | \square hyung-gun

Research Interests

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning for recognizing and reconstructing 3D objects. In this area, I applied machine learning (deep learning) algorithms for Augmented/Virtual Reality and Smart Factory.

Education

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT · Advisor: Karthik Ramani, Donald W.Feddersen Professor of Mechanical Engineering

Yonsei University Seoul, South Korea

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

• Advisor: Soo-Hong Lee, Full Professor of Mechanical Engineering

• 2011-2013, 2-year military service

Research Experience _

Mechanical Net C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Jan. 2019 - Present

- Collected massive mechanical component CAD data with a web-scrapper, and expanded the data for dense data distribution using Creo Parametric and SolidWorks API.
- Developed a web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network and PostgreSOL database.

FuseNet C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Present

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

• Built a Generative Adversarial Network which generates 3D objects given a discrete category condition and continuous instance-level attributes by fusing the various types of geometric information. (Relevant publication: [C2])

Latent Transformation Neural Network (LTNN)

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Feb. 2019

· Developed a fully-convolutional conditional generative network which is capable of view synthesis using a light-weight neural network suited for real-time applications. Introduced the conditional transformation unit which is designed to learn the latent space transformations corresponding to specified target views. (Relevant publication: [J4])

Visual Programming Language for Mobile Robots and IoT Nodes

C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Present

- · Proposed a web-based visual and spatial programming language that allows novice users and small industries to program mobile robots and IoT Nodes to execute planned tasks.
- · Developed a virtual world using Robotic Operating System(ROS) and GAZEBO which simulates interaction between mobile robots and IoT devices

ControllAR C-design LAB, Purdue Univ.

GRADUATE ASSISTANT

Aug. 2018 - Dec. 2018

• Proposed a parametrizing interface, simple and accessible fabrication workflow, and a pressure sensor using a soft piezoresistive elastomer material. Also, developed embedded system using Arduino and analyzed signals from different sensors and materials. (Relevant publication: [**J3**])

3D Object Classification Model Evaluation

Knowledge-Based Design Lab, Yonsie Univ.

UNDERGRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Feb. 2016 - Jul. 2017

· Proposed an evaluation method for 3D Deep Neural Networks by visualizing the impact of each voxel of each 3D objects and also a web-based 3D CAD search engine using a 3D Deep Neural Network for demonstration. (Relevant publication: [J2])

Web-based Surgical Workflow Management Platform

Knowledge-Based Design Lab, Yonsie Univ.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016

· Developed a web-based interface and database for integrated surgical information, to optimize surgical procedures and reduce the medical loss caused by communication errors and lack of information. (Relevant patent: [C1])

Working Experience

Python Developer Seoul, South Korea

FINANCIAL INSIGHT

Jan. 2018 - Jul. 2018

• Worked as a Python developer in an early-stage startup company. Developed a web-scrapper and database for collecting financial data of the Korean stock market.

Python Developer and CEO

Seoul, South Korea Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

NEIL LAB CORPORATION

• Developed an office automation system using Python specifically for automating tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts, and designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically scrap and integrate customer's financial and personal data. (*Relevant patent:* [P1])

• Founded and led a startup company as a CEO for a year and also worked as a Python developer. The company was funded \$ 30,000 by the Seongnam Industry Promotion Agency.

Mechanic and Squad leader

Inje, South Korea

REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY

Apr. 2011 – Jan. 2013

- Maintenanced military weapons and equipment including firearms and vehicles.
- Led a squad as a squad leader; honored as a distinguished soldier.

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C2][PDF] S. Kim, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. "FuseNet:Fusing surface and volumetric representations for 3D Shape Synthesis and Analysis" (2019) *International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)*, submitted.
- [C1][PDF] M. H. Woo, S. H. Kim, H. G. Chi, S. H. Lee, M. W. Park, and J. K. Kim. (2016) "Development of Web-based, Module Structure Platform for Surgical Workflow Management", *Proceedings of the Society for Computational Design and Engineering Conference*, 439-441.

Journal Papers

- [J4][PDF] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. G. Chi, G. Lin and Marthik Ramani. "Latent Transformations Neural Network for Object View Synthesis" (2019) *The Visual Computer*, submitted.
- [J3][PDF] L.Paredes, X. Qian, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. "ControllAR: Design and Fabrication of a Universal Parametric Low-Profile Hand Wearable for Augmented Reality Interactions" (2019) *Proceedings of the ACM on Interactive, Mobile, Wearable and Ubiquitous Technologies (IMWUT)*, submitted.
- [J2][PDF] H. T. Hwang, H. G. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. "An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification" (2019) *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)*, 33(3), 1333-1339.
- [J1][PDF] JIN YONGZHU, H. G. Chi and Soo-Hong Lee. (2016). A Study on the Optimal Design of Pedestrian Robots Using Janssen Mechanism. Korean Journal of Computational Design and Engineering Journal, 22(2), 18-22.

Patents

• [P1][PDF] H. G. Chi. "Computer Input Automation System" KR Patent (2017): 10-1745330.

Skills

Programming Python, C/C++, Matlab, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Frameworks TensorFlow, Keras, Caffe, PyTorch, ROS

Software Creo Parametric, SolidWorks, HyperWorks, GAZEBO

Honors & Awards

KISTI (Korea Institute of Science and Technology Information) President's Award,

Seoul, South Korea

Edison Challenge – Computer Aided Design Section

CDE (Korea Society for Computational Design and Engineering) President's Award,

CDE Challenge – Computational Design and Engineering Tools Section

Daejeon, South Korea

Extracurricular Activity

Habitat for Humanity Korea Campus Chapter

South Korea

• Constructed new houses for the homeless and renovated old houses, served more than 500 hours.

• Led and managed a volunteer group for a year; received the first honor from 2014 Yonsei Club Evaluation.

Korea Food for the Hungry International - campus volunteer group

South Korea

MEMBER

MEMBER & PRESIDENT

2016

Apr. 2013 - Nov. 2013

Mar. 2010 - Aug. 2016

 $\bullet \ \ \text{Mentored preschool children} \ \text{and elementary school students at the Seoul Children's Center} \\$